[
 {"question":"Passionate Slave", "answer":"Fervent Servant", "hint":"Fervent", "level": 8, "item":1, "completed": false, "id":215},
 {"question":"Narcoleptic Artwork", "answer":"Fainting Painting", "hint":"Fainting", "level": 8, "item":2, "completed": false, "id":216},
 {"question":"Used Clothing Problem", "answer":"Laundry Quandary", "hint":"Laundry", "level": 8, "item":3, "completed": false, "id":217},
 {"question":"Annoying Psyche", "answer":"Obnoxious Subconscious", "hint":"Obnoxious", "level": 8, "item":4, "completed": false, "id":218},
 {"question":"Bathing Suit Missile", "answer":"Speedo Torpedo", "hint":"Speedo", "level": 8, "item":5, "completed": false, "id":219},
 {"question":"Coastal Typewriter", "answer":"Seaboard Keyboard", "hint":"Seabord", "level": 8, "item":6, "completed": false, "id":220},
 {"question":"Dumb God of Love", "answer":"Stupid Cupid", "hint":"Stupid", "level": 8, "item":7, "completed": false, "id":221},
 {"question":"Flapjack Curtain", "answer":"Crepe Drape", "hint":"Crepe", "level": 8, "item":8, "completed": false, "id":222},
 {"question":"Perfect Spice", "answer":"Paragon Tarragon", "hint":"Paragon", "level": 8, "item":9, "completed": false, "id":223},
 {"question":"TV Uncertainty", "answer":"Television Indecision", "hint":"Television", "level": 8, "item":10, "completed": false, "id":224},
 {"question":"Moving Stair Teacher", "answer":"Escalator Educator", "hint":"Escalator", "level": 8, "item":11, "completed": false, "id":225},
 {"question":"Worshipping Baby Boomers", "answer":"Generation Veneration", "hint":"Generation", "level": 8, "item":12, "completed": false, "id":226},
 {"question":"Washable Head of School", "answer":"Rinsable Principle", "hint":"Rinsable", "level": 8, "item":13, "completed": false, "id":227},
 {"question":"Incognito Large African Animal", "answer":"Anonymous Hippopotamus", "hint":"Anonymous", "level": 8, "item":14, "completed": false, "id":228},
 {"question":"Icebox Mimic", "answer":"Refrigerator Imitator", "hint":"Refrigerator", "level": 8, "item":15, "completed": false, "id":229},
 {"question":"Justifying Being Untidy", "answer":"Disorganization Rationalization", "hint":"Disorganization", "level": 8, "item":16, "completed": false, "id":230},
 {"question":"Autocratic Pet Doctor", "answer":"Totalitarian Veterinarian", "hint":"Totalitarian", "level": 8, "item":17, "completed": false, "id":231},
 {"question":"Celebrate a Year of College", "answer":"University Anniversary", "hint":"University", "level": 8, "item":18, "completed": false, "id":232},
 {"question":"Speeding Creativity", "answer":"Imagination Acceleration", "hint":"Imagination", "level": 8, "item":19, "completed": false, "id":233},
 {"question":"Balanced Apartment", "answer":"Equilibrium Condominium", "hint":"Equilibrium", "level": 8, "item":20, "completed": false, "id":234}
 ]